A Guide to the Records of the Secretary of the Commonwealth, 1996-2006
Library of Virginia
- Series X. Restoration of Rights Files - Denied, 1997, 2003-2006 (accessions 42418 and 42513) RESTRICTED FOR 75 YEARS., Extent: 3.50 cu. ft. (Box 275-284, 287)
  Series documents the restoration of rights applications that were denied by Governor Mark R. Warner (2002-2006). Also included are a handful of applications denied by Governor George F. Allen (1994-1998). Each file includes a copy of the original application, rejection letter, recommendation letters, parole information, and police record checks. The files are arranged by year and alphabetically by name therein. This series contains confidential and privacy-protected information. Access is restricted for 75 years after date of creation per Code of Virginia 42.1-78.
  - 1997 (accession 42418)
    - Church, Elmer Clarence, denied 16 July 1997 (Box 287, Folder 6)
    - Crews, Charles Lee, denied 20 June 1997 (Box 287, Folder 6)
    - Crowder, Daniel Eugene, Sr., denied 20 June 1997 (Box 287, Folder 6)
    - D'Alexander, John Dominick, denied 11 July 1997 (Box 287, Folder 6)
    - Fields, Martin Jerome, denied 28 October 1997 (Box 287, Folder 7)
    - Hines, Shirley Temple, rights were never taken away (Box 287, Folder 7)
    - Mason, Joyce Regina, denied 16 July 1997 (Box 287, Folder 7)
  - 2003 (accession 42418)
    - Noland, Edmond Bruce, Jr., denied 23 February 2000 (Box 275, Folder 1)
    - Alford, Kara Yvette, denied 26 August 2003 (Box 275, Folder 2)
    - Atkins, Keith Franklin, denied 6 March 2003 (Box 275, Folder 2)
    - Bibb, Bradley Martin, denied 15 September 2003 (Box 275, Folder 2)
    - Brinkley, James Lee, denied 14 May 2003 (Box 275, Folder 3)
    - Brown, Joseph T., denied 14 May 2003 (Box 275, Folder 3)
    - Cash, Thomas Randolph, denied 5 August 2003 (Box 275, Folder 3)
    - Cok, Daniel Lee, denied 14 May 2003 (Box 275, Folder 3)
    - Downing, Elisa Nicole, denied 26 August 2003 (Box 275, Folder 4)
    - Emore, Paul Junior, denied 14 May 2003 (Box 275, Folder 4)
    - Evans, Michael David, denied 18 November 2003 (Box 275, Folder 4)
    - Flippen, Llewellyn T., denied 22 July 2003 (Box 275, Folder 4)
    - Fox, Robert Lee, denied 4 September 2003 (Box 275, Folder 4)
    - Gordon, Charles M., denied 6 March 2003 (Box 275, Folder 5)
    - Grant, Elizabeth Sibert, denied 6 March 2003 (Box 275, Folder 5)
    - Hall, Larry Edward, Jr., denied 5 August 2003 (Box 275, Folder 5)
    - Heisler, William Joseph, Jr., denied 6 March 2003 (Box 276, Folder 1)
    - Hudson, Jeffrey Lynn, denied 18 November 2003 (Box 276, Folder 1)
    - Johnson, Jimmie, denied 4 March 2003 (Box 276, Folder 1)
    - Johnson, Narlene Bethel, denied 5 August 2003 (Box 276, Folder 1)
    - Jones, John Henry, denied 15 September 2003 (Box 276, Folder 2)
    - Keen, Oadie Ray, Sr., denied 14 May 2003 (Box 276, Folder 2)
    - Kennedy, John Wallace, denied 6 March 2003 (Box 276, Folder 2)
    - McFaden, Timothy A., denied 6 March 2003 (Box 276, Folder 3)
    - McLaughlin, Sean M., denied 22 September 2003 (Box 276, Folder 3)
    - McWilliams, Willie C., denied 14 May 2003 (Box 276, Folder 4)
    - Martin, James D., denied 22 September 2003 (Box 276, Folder 4)
    - Neal, Bannister D., denied 22 September 2003 (Box 276, Folder 4)
    - Priet, John Trustan, Jr., denied 3 September 2003 (Box 276, Folder 5)
    - Pritchett, Jameson R., denied 15 September 2003 (Box 276, Folder 5)
    - Ramsey, Paul Delmar, denied 6 March 2003 (Box 276, Folder 5)
    - Scott, Sandra D., denied 22 September 2003 (Box 276, Folder 5)
    - Slaughter, Barbara A., denied 22 September 2003 (Box 276, Folder 6)
    - Stinson, Maynard Stephen, denied 5 August 2003 (Box 276, Folder 6)
    - Tignor, Barry Scott, denied 6 March 2003 (Box 276, Folder 6)
    - Trice, Stephen Taylor, denied 6 March 2003 (Box 276, Folder 6)
    - Waugh, Eddie M., denied 22 September 2003 (Box 277, Folder 1)
    - Webster, William E., denied 6 March 2003 (Box 277, Folder 1)
    - Woodson, Tony Vaton, denied 6 March 2003 (Box 277, Folder 1)
    - Yopp, Robert Allen, Sr., denied 26 August 2003 (Box 277, Folder 1)
  - 2004 (accession 42418)
    - Adkins, Harry Joseph, denied 12 March 2004 (Box 277, Folder 2)
    - Beavers, Dennis Dwight, denied 23 September 2004 (Box 277, Folder 2)
    - Boyd, Michael James, denied 16 September 2004 (Box 277, Folder 2)
    - Brandau, Jerry Ray, denied 21 June 2004 (Box 277, Folder 3)
    - Brown, Melvin Robert, denied 24 June 2004 (Box 277, Folder 3)
    - Cable, Sherman Ace, Jr., denied 25 August 2004 (Box 277, Folder 3)
    - Clapp, Wayne S., denied 21 June 2004 (Box 277, Folder 4)
    - Clifton, Anthony Dwayne, denied 21 June 2004 (Box 277, Folder 4)
    - Coleman, Frank Douglas, denied 24 June 2004 (Box 277, Folder 4)
    - Coleman, Jerry Lee, denied 21 June 2004 (Box 277, Folder 4)
    - Comer, Charles Blakely, denied 21 June 2004 (Box 277, Folder 5)
    - Crawley, Randy Lee, denied 25 August 2004 (Box 277, Folder 5)
    - Davis, Lewis Clay, denied 28 December 2004 (Box 277, Folder 5)
    - Delean, Priscilla, denied 15 March 2004 (Box 277, Folder 6)
    - Dolinger, Darrell Monroe, denied 21 June 2004 (Box 277, Folder 6)
    - Easter, Joel Edgar, Jr., denied 27 July 2004 (Box 278, Folder 1)
    - Eastlack, John William, Jr., denied 21 June 2004 (Box 278, Folder 1)
    - Elkins, Eric C., denied 18 February 2004 (Box 278, Folder 1)
    - Ellis, Rickie Lafayette, denied 22 October 2004 (Box 278, Folder 1)
    - Fitzgerald, Patrick Lee, denied 21 June 2004 (Box 278, Folder 2)
    - Fouse, Harry Gordon, Jr., denied 25 August 2004 (Box 278, Folder 2)
    - Frye, William Robert, denied 29 March 2004 (Box 278, Folder 2)
    - Giles, Larry Devon, denied 24 June 2004 (Box 278, Folder 2)
    - Green, Douglas Brad, denied 24 June 2004 (Box 278, Folder 3)
    - Grubb, David John, denied 24 June 2004 (Box 278, Folder 3)
    - Gunter, Jonathan Wayne, denied 21 June 2004 (Box 278, Folder 3)
    - Hackney, Sidney Allen, denied 21 June 2004 (Box 278, Folder 4)
    - Hartsook, William Henry, denied 24 June 2004 (Box 278, Folder 4)
    - Holland, George, Sr., denied 24 June 2004 (Box 278, Folder 4)
    - Holt, Mark Christopher, denied 12 March 2004 (Box 278, Folder 5)
    - Howard, Allen Theodore, Jr., denied 21 June 2004 (Box 278, Folder 5)
    - Howard, Willis Edward, denied 24 June 2004 (Box 278, Folder 5)
    - James, Jonathan N., denied 7 July 2004 (Box 278, Folder 5)
    - Jenkins, Anita Belle, denied 21 June 2004 (Box 278, Folder 5)
    - Johnson, Johnny Wayne, denied 24 June 2004 (Box 278, Folder 6)
    - Ketchum, Larry W., denied 24 June 2004 (Box 278, Folder 6)
    - Kitchen, Ricky James, denied 24 June 2004 (Box 278, Folder 6)
    - Knight, Larry Joe, denied 21 June 2004 (Box 278, Folder 6)
    - Lam, Joseph Henry, denied 21 June 2004 (Box 279, Folder 1)
    - Lucas, Jeffrey Jay, denied 24 June 2004 (Box 279, Folder 1)
    - Lucero, Lei Lani Kayrene, denied 22 June 2004 (Box 279, Folder 1)
    - Marroum, Rudolf Edward, denied 21 April 2004 (Box 279, Folder 2)
    - Maurice, Matthew Quentin, denied 12 August 2004 (Box 279, Folder 2)
    - Mooney, John Francis, denied 11 May 2004 (Box 279, Folder 3)
    - Moore, Calvin Ray, denied 6 July 2004 (Box 279, Folder 3)
    - Moore, Pamela Gay Dowell, denied 29 April 2004 (Box 279, Folder 3)
    - Mueller, Stephen Henry, denied 7 May 2004 (Box 279, Folder 4)
    - Mullins, Winfred Dewayne, denied 24 June 2004 (Box 279, Folder 4)
    - Newman-Stoner, Page Randolph, denied 24 June 2004 (Box 279, Folder 4)
    - Overton, Franklin David, denied 9 September 2004 (Box 279, Folder 4)
    - Padgett, Edward Lewis, denied 24 June 2004 (Box 279, Folder 5)
    - Passalaqua, Marcello, denied 24 June 2004 (Box 279, Folder 5)
    - Patel, Nileshkumar A., denied 29 March 2004 (Box 279, Folder 5)
    - Pedro, Charles Franklin, denied 24 June 2004 (Box 279, Folder 5)
    - Piersol, Kristen A., denied 24 June 2004 (Box 279, Folder 5)
    - Price, Dorothy Louise, denied 24 June 2004 (Box 280, Folder 1)
    - Robinson, Edward, Jr., denied 7 July 2004 (Box 280, Folder 1)
    - Robinson, Larry Maurice, denied 25 August 2004 (Box 280, Folder 1)
    - Schmitt, James L., denied 1 June 2004 (Box 280, Folder 1)
    - Sherod-White, Perlie Mae, denied 24 June 2004 (Box 280, Folder 1)
    - Shifflett, Freddie James, denied 24 June 2004 (Box 280, Folder 2)
    - Smith, David Edward, denied 16 June 2004 (Box 280, Folder 2)
    - Statton, James A., denied 24 June 2004 (Box 280, Folder 2)
    - Stephens, James Wheeler, denied 22 October 2004 (Box 280, Folder 2)
    - Stewart, Carroll, denied 1 December 2004 (Box 280, Folder 2)
    - Stickle, Robert Arthur, denied 24 June 2004 (Box 280, Folder 3)
    - Streater, Robert E., Jr., denied 27 September 2004 (Box 280, Folder 3)
    - Streightiff, Terry W., denied 9 July 2004 (Box 280, Folder 3)
    - Strickland, James N., Jr., denied 24 June 2004 (Box 280, Folder 3)
    - Taylor, Raymond Douglas, denied 12 March 2004 (Box 280, Folder 3)
    - Thompson, Joseph A., denied 23 November 2004 (Box 280, Folder 4)
    - Vaughan, Latasha Minggia, denied 25 August 2004 (Box 280, Folder 4)
    - Veth, Theodore, denied 24 June 2004 (Box 280, Folder 4)
    - Washington, Clyde Lesley, Jr., denied 24 June 2004 (Box 280, Folder 4)
    - Wells, David Keith, denied 10 August 2004 (Box 280, Folder 4)
    - White, Cornelius Bennie, denied 16 September 2004 (Box 280, Folder 5)
    - White, Ellen Reid, denied 12 April 2004 (Box 280, Folder 5)
    - Whittaker, Albert Edgar, Jr., denied 21 June 2004 (Box 280, Folder 5)
    - Wills, John Kevin, denied 24 June 2004 (Box 280, Folder 5)
    - Wilson, Alfred Antonio, denied 21 April 2004 (Box 280, Folder 6)
    - Wise, Kevin M., denied 13 April 2004 (Box 280, Folder 6)
    - Wright, Lloyd Wendall, denied 24 June 2004 (Box 280, Folder 6)
  - 2005-2006 (accession 42513)
    - Agee, Larry Douglas, denied 9 November 2005 (Box 281, Folder 1)
    - Allshouse, Carl Eugene, Sr., denied 15 June 2005 (Box 281, Folder 1)
    - Anderson, Henry, Jr., denied 3 February 2005 (Box 281, Folder 1)
    - Banks, James Patrick, Sr., denied 26 May 2005 (Box 281, Folder 1)
    - Barrett, Terry Anthony, denied 15 February 2005 (Box 281, Folder 1)
    - Beam, Phillip Henry, denied 18 July 2005 (Box 281, Folder 2)
    - Bell, Beverly Davis, Jr., denied 2 May 2005 (Box 281, Folder 2)
    - Blount, Linwood Roosevelt, Sr., denied 3 February 2005 (Box 281, Folder 2)
    - Brinkley, Colon, III, denied 5 July 2005 (Box 281, Folder 3)
    - Brinson, Stevie L., denied 5 July 2005 (Box 281, Folder 3)
    - Brooks, Lois Harper, denied 8 February 2005 (Box 281, Folder 3)
    - Campbell, Robert S., denied 23 March 2005 (Box 281, Folder 3)
    - Childress, Danny Kenwood, denied 15 June 2005 (Box 281, Folder 4)
    - Conner, Hugh Lester, deceased and denied 2005 (Box 281, Folder 4)
    - Cook, Ronald Lee, denied 29 March 2005 (Box 281, Folder 4)
    - Cooper, Neal Eugene, denied 13 July 2005 (Box 281, Folder 4)
    - Cosey, Glendolyn Moore, denied 26 August 2005 (Box 281, Folder 5)
    - Culver, David Windsor, denied 10 February 2005 (Box 281, Folder 5)
    - Davis, Casey Wayne, denied 14 November 2005 (Box 281, Folder 5)
    - Dick, Jeffrey Scott, denied 14 July 2005 (Box 281, Folder 5)
    - Eanes, Donald Lee, denied 29 September 2005 (Box 281, Folder 6)
    - Fiorillo, Antonio Dewayne, denied 26 August 2005 (Box 281, Folder 6)
    - Floyd, Clifton Alonzo, denied 13 December 2005 (Box 282, Folder 1)
    - Forte, Bedford Martin, III, denied 30 September 2005 (Box 282, Folder 1)
    - Foye, Angela Maria, denied 5 July 2005 (Box 282, Folder 1)
    - Green, Dainon Maurice, denied 24 October 2005 (Box 282, Folder 1)
    - Green, Walter H., Jr., denied 15 February 2005 (Box 282, Folder 2)
    - Grissom, Leonard, denied 8 February 2005 (Box 282, Folder 2)
    - Hancock, Lawrence Allen, denied 29 September 2005 (Box 282, Folder 2)
    - Harris, Denise A., denied 8 February 2005 (Box 282, Folder 2)
    - Harris, Ortha Ryland, denied 4 January 2006 (Box 282, Folder 3)
    - Harris, Tyrone, denied 8 February 2005 (Box 282, Folder 3)
    - Harvey, Larry Ray, denied 15 June 2005 (Box 282, Folder 3)
    - Hevener, Sterling Trent, denied 9 March 2005 (Box 282, Folder 3)
    - Hite, William Edward, denied 15 June 2005 (Box 282, Folder 3)
    - Hoggood, Joseph Aston, denied 15 June 2005 (Box 282, Folder 4)
    - Hollins, James E., III, denied 2 May 2005 (Box 282, Folder 4)
    - Islam, Abdul Jihad, denied 5 July 2005 (Box 282, Folder 4)
    - Jackson, Buddie Lee, denied 5 July 2005 (Box 282, Folder 4)
    - James, Dempsey Dean, Jr., denied 13 July 2005 (Box 282, Folder 5)
    - Jenkins, Willie Clinton, Jr., denied 4 January 2006 (Box 282, Folder 5)
    - Johnson, Alworth Anderson, denied 29 September 2005 (Box 282, Folder 5)
    - Jones, William Jeffery, denied 5 July 2005 (Box 282, Folder 5)
    - Keen, Clifford Wayne, denied 5 July 2005 (Box 282, Folder 6)
    - King, Wade Wilson, denied 15 June 2005 (Box 282, Folder 6)
    - Kovi, James Ronald, denied 8 February 2005 (Box 282, Folder 6)
    - Lamond, John Franklin, denied 15 June 2005 (Box 283, Folder 1)
    - Law, Amos, denied 21 September 2005 (Box 283, Folder 1)
    - Lewis, Carolyn Anne Bolin, denied 5 July 2005 (Box 283, Folder 1)
    - Liskey, David Scott, denied 21 September 2005 (Box 283, Folder 1)
    - Mason, Richard Oliver, IV, denied 21 March 2005 (Box 283, Folder 2)
    - Maxie, Robert David, denied 14 July 2005 (Box 283, Folder 2)
    - McDuffie, Carl Reo, denied 5 July 2005 (Box 283, Folder 2)
    - Mitchell, Terrence Nelson, denied 5 July 2005 (Box 283, Folder 2)
    - Murphy, Joseph H., denied 24 October 2005 (Box 283, Folder 2)
    - Moore, Sally J., denied 5 July 2005 (Box 283, Folder 3)
    - Morency, Scott James, denied 15 June 2005 (Box 283, Folder 3)
    - Nichols, Kenneth Lee, denied 1 November 2005 (Box 283, Folder 3)
    - Nickels, Jeffery Wayne, denied 5 July 2005 (Box 283, Folder 3)
    - Nixon, Gisela Altenkirch, denied 23 March 2005 (Box 283, Folder 3)
    - Pettiford, George Arlan, denied 26 August 2005 (Box 283, Folder 4)
    - Rainey, Rosemary Dawn, denied 5 July 2005 (Box 283, Folder 4)
    - Ramsey, Paul Delma, denied 5 July 2005 (Box 283, Folder 4)
    - Ricker, David W., denied 15 June 2005 (Box 283, Folder 4)
    - Robinson, Mitchell Dean, denied 15 February 2005 (Box 283, Folder 5)
    - Russell, James Leonard, Jr., denied 29 September 2005 (Box 283, Folder 5)
    - See, Justin Ward, denied 15 June 2005 (Box 283, Folder 5)
    - Sherman, Roger Lee, denied 14 July 2005 (Box 283, Folder 5)
    - Simmers, David Ross, denied 26 August 2005 (Box 283, Folder 5)
    - Skinner, Anthony Wayne, denied 13 July 2005 (Box 284, Folder 1)
    - Smith, Curtis Ray, denied 31 August 2005 (Box 284, Folder 1)
    - Sorrells, Tony Lee, denied 5 July 2005 (Box 284, Folder 1)
    - Stokes, John Manuel, denied 15 June 2005 (Box 284, Folder 2)
    - Strane, Christopher A., denied 13 July 2005 (Box 284, Folder 2)
    - Tanner, Mila Lee Ann, denied 26 August 2005 (Box 284, Folder 2)
    - Taylor, Bobby Lee, denied 15 June 2005 (Box 284, Folder 2)
    - Testerman, Wayne M., denied 4 January 2006 (Box 284, Folder 3)
    - Webster, William Eugene, denied 15 June 2005 (Box 284, Folder 3)
    - White, Carla Veronica, denied 5 July 2005 (Box 284, Folder 4)
    - Williams, Edwin T., denied 3 January 2006 (Box 284, Folder 4)
    - Williams, Erica Javon, denied 18 July 2005 (Box 284, Folder 4)
    - Wright, Ronald Sylvester, denied 30 November 2005 (Box 284, Folder 4)
    - Young, Buford Malcolm, denied 10 February 2005 (Box 284, Folder 4)